<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Caridion Arsenal (Continued)</name>
  <packageId>Mlie.CaridionArsenal</packageId>
  <author>Neildmac</author>
  <url>https://github.com/emipa606/CaridionArsenal</url>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.2</li>
    <li>1.3</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies />
  <loadAfter />
  <description>[img]https://i.imgur.com/buuPQel.png[/img]
Update of Neildmacs mod
https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=846378171

- Increased the weapons texture-resolution based on the forum-originals

[img]https://i.imgur.com/pufA0kM.png[/img]

[table]
    [tr]
        [td][url=https://invite.gg/Mlie][img]https://i.imgur.com/zdzzBrc.png[/img][/url][/td]
        [td][url=https://github.com/emipa606/CaridionArsenal][img]https://i.imgur.com/kTkpTOE.png[/img][/url][/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td][img]https://i.imgur.com/WjDSfUn.png[/img][/td]
        [td][img]https://i.imgur.com/Be8E2qJ.png[/img][/td]
    [/tr]
[/table]
	
[img]https://i.imgur.com/Z4GOv8H.png[/img]
Your typical weapons mod, in this case adding Charged weapons and misc weapons. All weapons can be crafted after the respective research is unlocked at the Machining table. Variants have their own quirks and values that allow for differing uses to their vanilla counterparts.

Not compatible with Combat Realism/Extended. Older versions are available on the forums.

Adds craftable weaponry to your colonists extra fun time on this desolate Rimworld! Includes: Flechette Shotgun, Charge Pistol, Charge SMG, Charge Carbine, Charge Shotgun, Charge LMG, Charge DMR, Charge Sniper, Charge Minigun, Potato Launcher, Flamethrower, Coilgun, Taser Pistol, Taser Rifle and the Hyperboreal Rifle


Additional details at: https://ludeon.com/forums/index.php?topic=29772.msg301969#msg301969

[img]https://i.imgur.com/PwoNOj4.png[/img]
[list]
[*] See if the the error persists if you just have this mod and its requirements active.
[*] If not, try adding your other mods until it happens again.
[*] Post your error-log using [url=https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=818773962]HugsLib[/url] and command Ctrl+F12
[*] For best support, please use the Discord-channel for error-reporting.
[*] Do not report errors by making a discussion-thread, I get no notification of that.
[*] If you have the solution for a problem, please post it to the GitHub repository.
[/list]
</description>
</ModMetaData>